
$( document ).ready(function() {

// create trivia questions 

var trivaQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is Ronâ€™s favorite whiskey?",
        choices: ["Jameson", "Jack Daniels", "Lagavulin", "Glenlivet"],
        correctChoice: 2
    },

    {
        question: "What month and day was Jerry born?",
        choices: [ "Feburary 29th", "April 1st", "April 20th", "WHY WAS HE EVEN BORN?!?" ],
        correctChoice: 0
    },

    {
        question: "Who is Chris Traeger's Therapist?",
        choices: ["Dr. Lu Saperstein", "Dr. Richard Nygard", "Dr. Harris", "Dr. Nick Newport"],
        correctChoice: 1
    },

    {
        question: "What country is Pawnee's sister city located in?",
        choices: ["France", "England", "Canada", "Venezuela"],
        correctChoice: 3
    },

    { 
        question: "What car make did Jean Ralphio get hit by to 'make money the old fashioned way'?",
        choices: [ "Audi", "BMW", "Lexus", "Mercedes"],
        correctChoice: 2
    },

    {
        question: "Who goes missing at the Harvest Festival?",
        choices: [ "Andy", "April", "Jerry", "Lil' Sebastian"],
        correctChoice: 3
    },

    {
        question: "What business did Tom Haverford start first?",
        choices: ["Entertainment 720", "SnakeHole Lounge", "Rent-a-Swag", "Tom's Bistro"],
        correctChoice: 0
    },

    {
        question: "What age does Chris Traeger plan on living to?",
        choices: ["100", "115", "120", "150"],
        correctChoice: 3
    },

    {
        question: "What department is the enemy of the Parks & Rec department?",
        choices:  ["Animal Care and Services","Library", "Sanitation", "Treasury"],
        correctChoice: 1
    },
      
    {
        question: "What is the name of Pawnee's pretentious and snotty neighbooring city?",
        choices: ["Anderson", "Eagleton", "Indianoplois", "Bloomington" ],
        correctChoice: 1
    }];


 var questionUp =0;
 var correctChoices = 0;

 
})

/* function playtrivia(){
        $(".triviaQ").text(trivaQuestions[i].question)
        trivaQuestions.length; i++
}




// answer options going with each question will get displayed in  a b c or d  choice class //

        $.each(trivaQuestions, function(){
            $(".choice1 .label-text").html(this.choices[0])
            $(".choice2 .label-text").html(this.choices[1])
            $(".choice3 .label-text").html(this.choices[2])
            $(".choice4 .label-text").html(this.choices[3])
           
        })
        
        playtrivia()
    })
    
    $(".next").on('click', function nextQ() {
       
    })



// game play//

// when player clicks to start game display questions and start timer for entire game //


// keep track of answers to keep score//

//if score above certain % celebrate gif displayed//
// if not above a good score, sad gif displayed//

*/
